<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  	<channel>
  		<title>
  			tipcofeed
  		</title>
  		<link>
  			http://www.tipco.com/wir
  		</link>
  		<description>
  			TIPCO RSS agg
  		</description>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				THE industrial revolution of the late 18th century made possible the mass production of goods, thereby creating economies of scale which changed the economy—and society—in ways that nobody could have imagined at the time. Now a new manufacturing technology has emerged which does the opposite. Three-dimensional printing makes it as cheap to create single items as it is to produce thousands and thus undermines economies of scale. It may have as profound an impact on the world as the coming of the factory did.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Fri, 11 Feb 2011 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Print me a Stradivarius: How a new manufacturing technology will change the world
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://media.economist.com/images/images-magazine/2011/02/12/ld/20110212_ldp001.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.economist.com/node/18114327
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.economist.com/node/18114327
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				What's the next big breakthrough for 3D printing? Try 3D-printed blood vessels. Last September, we looked at how researchers in Germany created printable blood vessels, but a research team from MIT and the University of Pennsylvania took the idea one step further. The latest breakthrough allows researchers to create entire networks of blood vessels using a sugar-based mixture and a customized RepRap 3D printer.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Tue, 03 Jul 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				3D Printer Uses Sugar to Create Blood Vessels
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.pcworld.com/article/258767/3d_printer_uses_sugar_to_create_blood_vessels.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.pcworld.com/article/258767/3d_printer_uses_sugar_to_create_blood_vessels.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				OPEN up any electronic device and inside there are circuit boards, components and bundles of wire. Assembling these items into a product like a phone can be a tedious, labour-intensive process, and one that is often subcontracted to low-wage countries such as China. Now new ways of printing electronics in three dimensions are being developed. This makes it possible to incorporate circuitry and components into the material the product is made from, such as the phone’s case. It could revolutionise the way electronic goods are made.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Sat, 28 Jul 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Print me a phone: New techniques to embed electronics into products
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.economist.com/node/21559593
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.economist.com/node/21559593
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				We’ve seen more than a handful of research projects with the goal to make robots look and feel more like us humans. A team of scientists from the University of Southern California's Viterbi School of Engineering is aiming specifically to make just a single artificial finger sensor, called BioTac, that can detect textures even better than a human can.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Tue, 19 Jun 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				USC Engineers Create a Robot Finger That Beats Humans at Feeling Textures
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://images.pcworld.com/images/article/2012/06/weird-11374724.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.pcworld.com/article/257893/usc_engineers_create_a_robot_finger_that_beats_humans_at_feeling_textures.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.pcworld.com/article/257893/usc_engineers_create_a_robot_finger_that_beats_humans_at_feeling_textures.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Researchers have found plenty of uses for carbon nanotubes, but a team at Stanford's of the Bao Research Group found a new use for them: artificial skin. The researchers created a stretchable, transparent skin-like sensor that not only is elastic like skin, but can also sense touch and pressure like the real thing.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Tue, 11 Oct 2011 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Artificial Skin Can Feel Touch; Robots Prepare to Out-Human Humans
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.techhive.com/article/242541/artificial_skin_can_feel_touch_robots_prepare_to_out_human_humans.html#tk.mod_stln
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.techhive.com/article/242541/artificial_skin_can_feel_touch_robots_prepare_to_out_human_humans.html#tk.mod_stln
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				There is great concern about China’s real-estate and infrastructure bubbles.  But these are just short-term challenges that China may be able to spend its way out of. The real threat to China’s economy is bigger and longer term: its manufacturing bubble.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Mon, 23 Jul 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				The End of Chinese Manufacturing and Rebirth of U.S. Industry
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://blogs-images.forbes.com/singularity/files/2012/07/Tesla-Manufacturing.png" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.forbes.com/sites/singularity/2012/07/23/the-end-of-chinese-manufacturing-and-rebirth-of-u-s-industry/
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.forbes.com/sites/singularity/2012/07/23/the-end-of-chinese-manufacturing-and-rebirth-of-u-s-industry/
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				The unattended steering wheel on the 15-ton military truck jerked sharply back and forth as the vehicle's huge tires bounced down a rain-scarred ravine through mounds of mine rubble on a rugged hillside near Pittsburgh.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 09 May 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				U.S. military embraces robots with greater autonomy
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.reuters.com/article/2012/05/09/us-usa-defense-robots-idUSBRE84805N20120509
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.reuters.com/article/2012/05/09/us-usa-defense-robots-idUSBRE84805N20120509
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Last week, Cisco announced its intended acquisition of relatively unknown Silicon Photonics startup Lightwire, for $271M – not exactly chump change. (For those unfamiliar with the term Silicon Photonics, it is a technology where complex photonic devices are integrated and manufactured using well-known semiconductor technologies to enable ultra-high-speed communications.) The reaction to this announcement was so strong that Jefferies downgraded Cisco-supplier Finisar, a maker of more traditional optical networking components.  
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				The Race for Photon Supremacy, in Silicon
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.forbes.com/sites/joshwolfe/2012/03/02/the-race-for-photon-supremacy-in-silicon/
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.forbes.com/sites/joshwolfe/2012/03/02/the-race-for-photon-supremacy-in-silicon/
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				A team of professors and scientists have developed a laser that goes on a &quot;seek and destroy&quot; mission to non-invasively destroy cancerous tumors.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 25 Jul 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Researchers Invent Cancer-Fighting Laser
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.pcmag.com/article2/0,2817,2407633,00.asp
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.pcmag.com/article2/0,2817,2407633,00.asp
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				GRAPHENE, a form of carbon that comes in sheets a single atom thick, has gained a reputation as a wonder material. It is the best conductor yet discovered of heat at room temperature and is 40 times stronger than steel. It is also a semiconductor whose electrical conductivity is 1,000 times better than silicon's. This means it could be used to make devices far more sensitive than is possible now, leading some to predict that it will one day become the material of choice for computer chips. There was little surprise, therefore, when Andre Geim (pictured above) and Konstantin Novoselov, two physicists who were investigating graphene's structure, won the 2010 Nobel prize for their work.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Sat, 12 May 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Graphene shows its colours
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://media.economist.com/sites/default/files/imagecache/full-width/images/print-edition/20120512_STP002_0.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.economist.com/node/21554503
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.economist.com/node/21554503
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				THE phrase “indoor solar power” sounds like an oxymoron. But there is growing interest in the idea of using photoelectric cells to run gadgets as well as power grids—and doing so even when those gadgets are inside buildings. Much of the light these cells used would, of necessity, come from incandescent bulbs, fluorescent tubes and light-emitting diodes (LEDs) rather than through the window from the sun. But if the right sorts of cells were available this could be cheaper than constantly replacing the batteries that currently power electronic gizmos.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Thu, 12 Apr 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				To dye for: A new type of cell may bring “solar” energy indoors
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.economist.com/node/21552537
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.economist.com/node/21552537
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Scientists at Japanese tech company Burton Inc. have developed a way to display images in the air or water without using a physical screen.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 16 Nov 2011 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				This true 3D hologram display is the future
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.cbsnews.com/8301-501465_162-57325986-501465/this-true-3d-hologram-display-is-the-future/
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.cbsnews.com/8301-501465_162-57325986-501465/this-true-3d-hologram-display-is-the-future/
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Rohde &amp; Schwarz introduces the new R&amp;S ESR EMI test receiver whose broadband architecture allows standard-compliant EMI measurements up to 6000 times faster than other solutions. Comprehensive diagnostic tools such as spectrogram display, realtime spectrum analysis and IF analysis help developers detect and eliminate EMI. The R&amp;S ESR is impressively easy to use thanks to its intuitive touchscreen interface.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Tue, 07 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				The R&amp;S®ESR, the world's fastest EMI test receiver, reduces testing times and more reliably detects EMI
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www2.rohde-schwarz.com/en/news_events/news/news-The_R%26S%C2%AEESR%2C_the_world%27s_fastest_EMI_test_receiver%2C_reduces_testing_times_and_more_reliably_detects_EMI.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www2.rohde-schwarz.com/en/news_events/news/news-The_R%26S%C2%AEESR%2C_the_world%27s_fastest_EMI_test_receiver%2C_reduces_testing_times_and_more_reliably_detects_EMI.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				The largest-ever experiment in space has reported the collection of some 18 billion &quot;cosmic ray&quot; events that may help unravel the Universe's mysteries.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 25 Jul 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Alpha Magnetic Spectrometer claims huge cosmic ray haul
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://news.bbcimg.co.uk/media/images/61807000/jpg/_61807635_61807631.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-18928177
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-18928177
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Three Ocean Optics instruments have completed their eight month journey to Mars to study soil composition as part of the ChemCam mission. NASA’s Mars Science Lab rover, Curiosity, was launched last November carrying customized Ocean Optics HR2000 spectrometers.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Fri, 10 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Ocean Optics Spectrometers Land Safely on Mars
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.photonicsonline.com/doc.mvc/ocean-optics-spectrometers-land-safely-on-mars-0001
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.photonicsonline.com/doc.mvc/ocean-optics-spectrometers-land-safely-on-mars-0001
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				GRESHAM — A lone contractor plugged away at a laptop Thursday in a gleaming chemical processing plant about to open at Boeing’s factory complex in Gresham.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Fri, 10 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Boeing expands Gresham facility that will manufacture airplane parts
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.statesmanjournal.com/viewart/20120811/NEWS/308110023/Boeing-expands-Gresham-facility-will-manufacture-airplane-parts?odyssey=nav%7Chead
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.statesmanjournal.com/viewart/20120811/NEWS/308110023/Boeing-expands-Gresham-facility-will-manufacture-airplane-parts?odyssey=nav%7Chead
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Corning Incorporated (NYSE: GLW) today hosted a grand opening and groundbreaking ceremony for Corning (Shanghai) Co. Ltd., Corning’s wholly owned automotive substrate facility in Shanghai, China. The event celebrated the completion of a $125 million expansion and the beginning of a previously announced third capacity build-out. Members of the Chinese government, customers, and employees attended the ceremony.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Tue, 15 May 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Corning Holds Grand Opening Ceremony for Shanghai Automotive Substrate Facility Expansion
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.corning.com/news_center/news_releases/2012/2012051501.aspx
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.corning.com/news_center/news_releases/2012/2012051501.aspx
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Fast pace, low margins have online retailers looking to automation to keep up
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Fri, 20 Jul 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				In Warehouses, Kiva's Robots Do the Heavy Lifting
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://www.technologyreview.com/files/88989/br.video.kiva_x296.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.technologyreview.com/news/428436/in-warehouses-kivas-robots-do-the-heavy-lifting/
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.technologyreview.com/news/428436/in-warehouses-kivas-robots-do-the-heavy-lifting/
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Maybe it's time to shelve the old saying, &quot;you can't leave home without it,&quot; when it comes to packing for trips to space.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Thu, 19 Jul 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Made-in-Space Parts Could Become Space Travel's New Norm
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.space.com/16656-space-manufacturing-3d-printing.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.space.com/16656-space-manufacturing-3d-printing.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				A company that's developing inflatable satellite components won the $100,000 grand prize in a space business contest Saturday.  Space Ground Amalgam, LLC took home first place in the 2012 NewSpace Business Plan Competition, which seeks to help startup space firms create potentially game-changing technologies. The Virginia-based company beat out nine other finalists for the NASA-funded prize, which was announced Saturday night at the NewSpace 2012 conference awards gala in Santa Clara, Calif.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Tue, 31 Jul 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Space prize goes to company making inflatable satellite parts: $100,000 for first place doled out in NASA-backed NewSpace 2012 conference awards
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/48421516/ns/technology_and_science-space/#.UCgY18ie624
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/48421516/ns/technology_and_science-space/#.UCgY18ie624
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				IPG Photonics (NASDAQ: IPGP) posted higher-than-anticipated revenues and profits in 2Q12, citing solid business particularly in automotive and consumer electronics, and says the near-term outlook is strong despite some macroeconomic sluggishness in several regions (e.g. Europe and China).
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Tue, 31 Jul 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				IPG beats estimates in 2Q12, sees brightening horizons in Europe and Asia
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.industrial-lasers.com/articles/2012/07/ipg-beats-estimates-in-2q12-sees-brightening-horizons-in-europe-and-asia.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.industrial-lasers.com/articles/2012/07/ipg-beats-estimates-in-2q12-sees-brightening-horizons-in-europe-and-asia.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Applied Industrial Technologies AIT today reported results for its fourth quarter and fiscal 2012 year ended June 30, 2012.  Fiscal 2012 full-year sales were a record $2.4 billion, up 7.3% from fiscal 2011 sales of $2.2 billion. Net income for the year increased to a record $108.8 million, or $2.54 per share, compared with $96.8 million, or $2.24 per share, in fiscal 2011. 
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Thu, 09 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Applied Industrial Technologies Reports Record Sales and Earnings for Fiscal 2012
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://money.msn.com/business-news/article.aspx?feed=PR&amp;date=20120809&amp;id=15432940
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://money.msn.com/business-news/article.aspx?feed=PR&amp;date=20120809&amp;id=15432940
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				The world's largest oilfield services provider, Schlumberger Limited ( SLB ), has been contracted by Poltava Petroleum Company - a wholly owned subsidiary of UK-listed JKX Oil &amp; Gas - for multi-stage fracture stimulation intended for a well in Ukraine. 
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Fri, 10 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Schlumberger Wins Multi Frac Job - Analyst Blog
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://community.nasdaq.com/News/2012-08/schlumberger-wins-multi-frac-job-analyst-blog.aspx?storyid=163087
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://community.nasdaq.com/News/2012-08/schlumberger-wins-multi-frac-job-analyst-blog.aspx?storyid=163087
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Water smart grid technology provider Sensus has acquired a 15% equity position in Brazilian smart grid vendor CAS Tecnologia (CAS) to distribute its Hemera utility data management platform.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Tue, 07 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Smart water grid expansion in Brazil for Sensus
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.waterworld.com/articles/2012/08/smart-water-grid-expansion-in-brazil-for-sensus.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.waterworld.com/articles/2012/08/smart-water-grid-expansion-in-brazil-for-sensus.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				The biggest innovation in the solar industry in recent years has been financial rather than technological – letting homeowners lease photovoltaic panels and avoid the steep upfront capital cost of going solar. That has driven the pell-mell growth of solar installers like SolarCity, SunRun and Sungevity even through the depths of the Great Recession.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Thu, 09 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Photovoltaic Manufacturers See Profit In Solar Leases Amid Market Upheaval
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://blogs-images.forbes.com/toddwoody/files/2012/08/300px-Solar_panels_on_house_roof.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.forbes.com/sites/toddwoody/2012/08/09/photovoltaic-manufacturers-see-profit-in-solar-leases-amid-market-upheaval/
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.forbes.com/sites/toddwoody/2012/08/09/photovoltaic-manufacturers-see-profit-in-solar-leases-amid-market-upheaval/
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				The U.S. Army is looking for a few good renewable energy projects. Some $7 billion worth.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 08 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				U.S. Army Opens Bids To Buy $7 Billion In Renewable Energy
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.forbes.com/sites/toddwoody/2012/08/08/u-s-army-opens-bids-to-buy-7-billion-in-renewable-energy/
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.forbes.com/sites/toddwoody/2012/08/08/u-s-army-opens-bids-to-buy-7-billion-in-renewable-energy/
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Cobalt Technologies, a leading developer of next generation bio-based chemicals and specialty chemical company Rhodia, member of the Solvay Group, today announced they will begin joint development and operation of a biobutanol demonstration facility in Brazil. This is one more step by the two companies toward the construction of commercial-scale biorefineries using Cobalt's technology to convert Brazilian bagasse and other local non-food feedstock into bio n-butanol in Latin America.  Butanol is widely used as an industrial chemical found in paints, adhesives, inks, and other solvents.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 01 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Cobalt Technologies and Rhodia to Build Bio n-Butanol Demonstration Facility in Latin America
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://blogs-images.forbes.com/toddwoody/files/2012/08/300px-Nellis_AFB_Solar_panels.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.sacbee.com/2012/08/01/4680989/cobalt-technologies-and-rhodia.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.sacbee.com/2012/08/01/4680989/cobalt-technologies-and-rhodia.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				GE Healthcare has started designing a vaccine manufacturing facility a drug company, just days after expanding its collaboration with plant-cell production technology firm iBio.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 01 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				GE and iBio designing plant-cell based vaccine facility
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://www.in-pharmatechnologist.com/var/plain_site/storage/images/publications/pharmaceutical-science/in-pharmatechnologist.com/processing/ge-and-ibio-designing-plant-cell-based-vaccine-facility/7207377-1-eng-GB/GE-and-iBio-designing-plant-cell-based-vaccine-facility_dnm_headline.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.in-pharmatechnologist.com/Processing/GE-and-iBio-designing-plant-cell-based-vaccine-facility
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.in-pharmatechnologist.com/Processing/GE-and-iBio-designing-plant-cell-based-vaccine-facility
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Aluminum giant Alcoa Inc. ( AA ) has announced that its Alcoa Oil and Gas Division has set up a 1800 meters (5,905 feet) long Aluminum Alloy Drill Pipe (AADP) in the Iron Duke Well C offshore Seria, Brunei. The company has collaborated with Brunei Shell Petroleum Co. (&quot;BSP&quot;) and AMRTUR Corp. on the project
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Fri, 10 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Alcoa deploys horizontal drill  in Brunei
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://community.nasdaq.com/News/2012-08/alcoa-deploys-drill-pipe-in-brunei-analyst-blog.aspx?storyid=163041
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://community.nasdaq.com/News/2012-08/alcoa-deploys-drill-pipe-in-brunei-analyst-blog.aspx?storyid=163041
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				When I was a kid, we'd all pile into the Country Squire for the long trip north to see the Boston branch of the family. On one trip we stopped in Corning, N.Y., so my mother could pay her respects at the Corning Glass museum, and perhaps pick up a casserole dish or two. All I knew about Corning (NYSE: GLW  ) at the time was that the company had something to do with many of my favorite meals, and confusingly had nothing to do with corn itself.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Tue, 14 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				What's So Special About Gorilla Glass 2?
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.fool.com/investing/general/2012/08/14/whats-so-special-about-gorilla-glass-2.aspx
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.fool.com/investing/general/2012/08/14/whats-so-special-about-gorilla-glass-2.aspx
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				At the Philips Electronics factory on the coast of China, hundreds of workers use their hands and specialized tools to assemble electric shavers. That is the old way.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Sat, 18 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Skilled Work, Without the Worker
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://graphics8.nytimes.com/images/2012/08/19/business/JP-ROBOT-1/JP-ROBOT-1-articleLarge.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.nytimes.com/2012/08/19/business/new-wave-of-adept-robots-is-changing-global-industry.html?_r=1&amp;ref=technology
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.nytimes.com/2012/08/19/business/new-wave-of-adept-robots-is-changing-global-industry.html?_r=1&amp;ref=technology
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Taiwanese electronics manufacturer Foxconn Technology, has decided to open a factory in Serang, Banten. The plant which will produce 10 million units per year of electronic tools and will occupy an area of ​​5,000 square meters.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 15 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Foxconn to Build Plant in Cikande
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.tempointeractive.com/hg/nasional/2012/08/15/brk,20120815-423779,uk.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.tempointeractive.com/hg/nasional/2012/08/15/brk,20120815-423779,uk.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Every year, 2.1 million people die from vaccine-preventable disease—and it’s no mystery why a good number go without the immunizations that could save lives. Many live off-grid without electricity—and no refrigerators to keep vaccines cold in clinics. Without being chilled between 35-45 degrees Fahrenheit (2-8 degrees Celsius), vaccines spoil and become inactive. 
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Fri, 17 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Nanotech &quot;Jackets&quot; to Keep Vaccines From Spoiling Off-Grid
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://pre.cloudfront.goodinc.com/posts/full_1345164458photo(39).jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.good.is/post/nanotech-jackets-to-keep-vaccines-from-spoiling-off-grid/
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.good.is/post/nanotech-jackets-to-keep-vaccines-from-spoiling-off-grid/
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				New findings show that the material beneath the thin carbon sheets determines how they react chemically and electrically.  When you look at a gift-wrapped present, the basic properties of the wrapping paper — say, its colors and texture — are not generally changed by the nature of the gift inside. 
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Mon, 13 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Graphene’s behavior depends on where it sits
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://img.mit.edu/newsoffice/images/article_images/20120810145516-0.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://web.mit.edu/newsoffice/2012/graphene-electrons-behavior-0813.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://web.mit.edu/newsoffice/2012/graphene-electrons-behavior-0813.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Tokelau may not yet be a fully self-governing country—the major of its budget is paid for in aid from New Zealand; its citizens still are technically citizens of New Zealand; and it has non-self-governing territory status with the UN—but its may well become the world's nation of island to get all of its electricity from solar power.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 01 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Tokelau Will Be World's First 100% Solar Powered Nation by September
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://media.treehugger.com/assets/images/2012/08/20120801-fakaofo-atoll-tokelau.jpg.492x0_q85_crop-smart.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.treehugger.com/renewable-energy/tokelau-world-first-100-percent-solar-powered-nation-september.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.treehugger.com/renewable-energy/tokelau-world-first-100-percent-solar-powered-nation-september.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Peter Thiel's philanthropic foundation gives up to $350,000 to a company named Modern Meadow, which plans to use 3D bioprinting to create an &quot;edible prototype&quot; that's a meat replacement.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 15 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				3D printed meat: It's what's for dinner
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://news.cnet.com/8301-11386_3-57493377-76/3d-printed-meat-its-whats-for-dinner/
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://news.cnet.com/8301-11386_3-57493377-76/3d-printed-meat-its-whats-for-dinner/
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				A solar-powered toilet that converts human waste into electricity snags first place—and $100,000—at the Reinvent the Toilet Challenge.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Fri, 17 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Eco-friendly Flush
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://the-scientist.com/2012/08/17/eco-friendly-flush/
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://the-scientist.com/2012/08/17/eco-friendly-flush/
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Even after 18 years of frozen storage, human embryos can still produce viable stem cells for drug screening and biomedical research.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Thu, 16 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Embryonic Stem Cells Survive Freezing
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://the-scientist.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/Embryo_8_cells-sm.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://the-scientist.com/2012/08/16/embryonic-stem-cells-survive-freezing/
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://the-scientist.com/2012/08/16/embryonic-stem-cells-survive-freezing/
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				For nearly 30 years lead singer Bruce Dickinson has been know worldwide as the voice of heavy metal band Iron Maiden. It's easy to see he has a passion for his music, but there's another kind of metal he's equally passionate about, airplanes. “It's pretty much like breathing really. It's one of those essential things,” says Dickinson.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Mon, 13 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Iron Maiden lead singer rocks 747-8 simulator
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.boeing.com/Features/2012/08/bca_ironmaiden_08_13_12.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.boeing.com/Features/2012/08/bca_ironmaiden_08_13_12.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				With financial support from the U.S. National Institutes of Health and the National Science Foundation, the biomedical engineers have developed a biochip that detects traces of influenza by honing in on RNA sequence and then using the magnets to separate the sequence from the rest of the RNA strand, according research published in the Journal of Molecular Diagnostics.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Fri, 15 Jun 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Brown University researchers create flu-detection test
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.masshightech.com/stories/2012/06/11/daily53-Brown-University-researchers-create-flu-detection-test.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.masshightech.com/stories/2012/06/11/daily53-Brown-University-researchers-create-flu-detection-test.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				A team of researchers led by George Whitesides, the Woodford L. and Ann A. Flowers University Professor, has already broken new engineering ground with the development of soft, silicone-based robots inspired by creatures like starfish and squid.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Thu, 16 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Soft Robots' Could Camouflage Themselves One Minute, and Stand Out, the Next
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://images.sciencedaily.com/2012/08/120816141535-large.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2012/08/120816141535.htm
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2012/08/120816141535.htm
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Pioneering mass spectrometry methods developed at the U.S. Department of Energy’s (DOE’s) Ames Laboratory are helping plant biologists get their first glimpses of never-before-seen plant tissue structures. The new method opens up new realms of study, ones that might have long-ranging implications for biofuels research and crop genetics.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 15 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Spectrometry Method Reveals Previously Hidden Plant Tissues 
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://www.laboratoryequipment.com/sites/laboratoryequipment.com/files/legacyimages/0712/081512_lw_tissues.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.laboratoryequipment.com/news/2012/08/spectrometry-method-reveals-previously-hidden-plant-tissues
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.laboratoryequipment.com/news/2012/08/spectrometry-method-reveals-previously-hidden-plant-tissues
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				An unmanned experimental aircraft designed to fly six times the speed of sound broke apart over the Pacific Ocean seconds into a military test flight due to a faulty control fin, the U.S. Air Force said on Wednesday.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Thu, 16 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				U.S. hypersonic aircraft crashes seconds into military test flight
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://in.reuters.com/article/2012/08/16/us-usa-hypersonic-flight-idINBRE87F08X20120816
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://in.reuters.com/article/2012/08/16/us-usa-hypersonic-flight-idINBRE87F08X20120816
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Today, NASA's Mars rover Curiosity fired its laser for the first time on Mars, using the beam from a science instrument to interrogate a fist-size rock called &quot;Coronation.&quot; The mission's Chemistry and Camera instrument, or ChemCam, hit the fist-sized rock with 30 pulses of its laser during a 10-second period. Each pulse delivers more than a million watts of power for about five one-billionths of a second. 
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Sun, 19 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Rover's Laser Instrument Zaps First Martian Rock
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://www.jpl.nasa.gov/images/msl/20120819/pia16075-640.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.cfm?release=2012-248
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/news.cfm?release=2012-248
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				3-D printing has yielded items both fascinating and potentially troubling. Now we can add one more to the list of printed achievements: The U.S. Army has had a rapid prototyping wing for some time, and now they've deployed full teams--complete with scientists and 3-D printers--to Afghanistan.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Tue, 21 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Army Sends Mobile 3-D Printing Labs to Afghanistan For On-Demand Gear
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://www.popsci.com/files/imagecache/article_image_large/articles/army-file.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.popsci.com/technology/article/2012-08/army-sends-shipping-containers-mobile-3-d-printing-labs-afghanistan
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.popsci.com/technology/article/2012-08/army-sends-shipping-containers-mobile-3-d-printing-labs-afghanistan
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Scientists weigh in on the hydraulic fracturing debate
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Sat, 08 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				The Facts Behind the Frack 
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://www.sciencenews.org/pictures/090812/feat_fracking_production_zoom.gif" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.sciencenews.org/view/feature/id/343202/title/The_Facts_Behind_the_Frack
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.sciencenews.org/view/feature/id/343202/title/The_Facts_Behind_the_Frack
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				A joint venture of Tomball-based JBL Energy Partners and Terrace Energy of Fort Worth has begun horizontal drilling in the Woodbine play north of Houston, JBL said Thursday. JBL, a privately held oil and gas exploration and production company, announced at the same time that it has completed the sale of 17,000 acres within the Woodbine play to Halcón Resources Corp.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Thu, 23 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Venture drilling in play north of Houston
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.chron.com/business/article/Venture-drilling-in-play-north-of-Houston-3811304.php
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.chron.com/business/article/Venture-drilling-in-play-north-of-Houston-3811304.php
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Now that Airbus is opening a U.S. plant, Washington's economy will benefit from an uptick in demand for all the parts and equipment needed to build next-generation aircraft. 
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Sun, 26 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Op-ed: U.S. Airbus plant boon for state's aerospace suppliers
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://seattletimes.nwsource.com/html/opinion/2018987383_guestnancymclernonxml.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://seattletimes.nwsource.com/html/opinion/2018987383_guestnancymclernonxml.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				The NASA rover Curiosity made its first test drive Wednesday on ancient soil of Mars. The rover moved forward about 15 feet, rotated to a right angle and reversed a short distance. The drive was successful. (Aug. 22)
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 22 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				NASA Rover Curiosity Makes First Mars Trip 
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tULvuOXtBO0&amp;feature=player_embedded
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tULvuOXtBO0&amp;feature=player_embedded
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				By combining bouncing photons, the particles of light, with advanced  optics, researchers are able to “see” 3D images of objects hidden around a corner. 
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Tue, 07 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Laser Can See Through Solid Walls 
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://www.laboratoryequipment.com/sites/laboratoryequipment.com/files/legacyimages/0712/080712_laser.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.laboratoryequipment.com/news/2012/08/laser-can-see-through-solid-walls
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.laboratoryequipment.com/news/2012/08/laser-can-see-through-solid-walls
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Hillsboro, Ore.-based solar manufacturer SolarWorld says it has made new investments totaling &amp;#036;27 million to upgrade and replace several factory systems and debut technological advances that are expected to boost the power output of its modules.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Tue, 07 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				SolarWorld Upgrades Factory Through $27M Investment 
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://solarindustrymag.com/e107_plugins/content/content.php?content.10901
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://solarindustrymag.com/e107_plugins/content/content.php?content.10901
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Solar Impulse, a huge experimental solar-powered plane, landed in Morocco's capital late on Tuesday night after a 20-hour trip from Madrid in the first transcontinental journey by a craft of its type.&quot;It was perhaps the most beautiful flight of my life, I have dreamed since I was a child of flying without using fuel,&quot; said Swiss pilot Bertrand Piccard, who has already circumnavigated the world by balloon, on arrival at Rabat’s International airport.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Mon, 04 Jun 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Solar plane ends first intercontinental flight
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.swissinfo.ch/eng/science_technology/Solar_plane_ends_first_intercontinental_flight.html?cid=32845224
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.swissinfo.ch/eng/science_technology/Solar_plane_ends_first_intercontinental_flight.html?cid=32845224
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Trimble has entered into a definitive agreement to acquire privately-held TMW Systems Inc., a provider of enterprise software to transportation and logistics companies, for $335 million. 
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Mon, 27 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Trimble Acquires TMW Systems for $335 Million
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://mhlnews.com/news/trimble-acquires-tmw-systems/
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://mhlnews.com/news/trimble-acquires-tmw-systems/
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				This is part of a 30-part series called &quot;Game Changers.&quot; This special series investigates the most remarkable advancements in science, energy and health — and how they will impact the way we live. This series is brought to you by Samsung's Galaxy S3.  Great ideas happen every day, but few have the power to change the world.   These innovations in health, energy, space and transportation are poised to make a serious impact on the future.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 15 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				30 Innovations That Will Change The World
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://static1.businessinsider.com/image/502b9d136bb3f7e12c00000c-400-300/game-changers-rocket.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.businessinsider.com/30-game-changing-innovations-2012-8
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.businessinsider.com/30-game-changing-innovations-2012-8
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				http://www.businessinsider.com/game-changers-list-2012-7#ixzz26kckg0aK
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Thu, 30 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Areion: The world’s first (mostly) 3D-printed electric racecar
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://cdn4.digitaltrends.com/wp-content/uploads/cache/2012/08/Areion-The-worlds-first-mostly-3D-printed-electric-racecar/2880775605.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.digitaltrends.com/cars/areion-the-worlds-first-mostly-3d-printed-electric-racecar/
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.digitaltrends.com/cars/areion-the-worlds-first-mostly-3d-printed-electric-racecar/
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				The satellite remote sensing images of the Huangyan Island, Diaoyu Islands and Xisha Islands have been included in the state's dynamic monitoring and management system, according to the State Oceanic Administration of China. It is another great progress since the dynamic monitoring and management system of the waters began implementing regular monitoring to the offshore area of China. 
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Tue, 04 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				China improves far-sea territory monitoring
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://english.peopledaily.com.cn/mediafile/201209/04/F201209041502112478116965.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://english.peopledaily.com.cn/90785/7935643.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://english.peopledaily.com.cn/90785/7935643.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Qbotix Inc., a closely held robotics company, is developing systems that may cut the cost of energy from solar farms by as much as 20 percent. Its robotics technology is an alternative to currently available dual-axis or single-axis tracking systems, which rotate solar panels toward the sun to increase energy production, according to Wasiq Bokhari, Qbotix’s chief executive officer. “We are the first company to use mobile, intelligent robots to operate solar power plants,” he said in a phone interview. 
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Thu, 06 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Qbotix Sees Tiny Robots Reducing Solar Costs, Boosting Output
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://www.designboom.com/weblog/images/images_2/andrea/robots/solbot01.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.businessweek.com/news/2012-09-04/qbotix-sees-tiny-robots-reducing-solar-costs-boosting-output
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.businessweek.com/news/2012-09-04/qbotix-sees-tiny-robots-reducing-solar-costs-boosting-output
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				A Wave Glider wave-powered autonomous marine robot from Liquid Robotics, an ocean data service provider, stared down Hurricane Isaac while collecting ocean chemistry data in the Gulf of Mexico. 
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Tue, 04 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Liquid Robotics Wave Glider battles Hurricane Isaac
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://www.militaryaerospace.com/content/mae/en/articles/2012/09/liquid-robotics/_jcr_content/leftcolumn/article/headerimage.img.jpg/1346721641814.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.militaryaerospace.com/articles/2012/09/liquid-robotics.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.militaryaerospace.com/articles/2012/09/liquid-robotics.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				The National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) has successfully launched two Mars Exploration Rovers on seven-month journeys to Mars. The Rovers are outfitted with BAE SYSTEMS radiation-hardened RAD6000 computers that will process and send data back to earth to help NASA search for evidence about ancient water on Mars. The first launch occurred June 10 from Kennedy Space Center
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Fri, 07 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				BAE chips enroute to Mars
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://www.21stcentury.co.uk/images/technology/bae_mars_main.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.21stcentury.co.uk/technology/bae_mars.asp
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.21stcentury.co.uk/technology/bae_mars.asp
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Physicists have &quot;teleported&quot; quantum information farther than ever in a new study reported Wednesday (Sept. 5).This kind of teleportation isn't quite what Scotty was &quot;beaming up&quot; on television's Star Trek, but it does represent a kind of magic of its own. While Star Trek's teleporters transport people from place to place instantaneously, quantum teleportation sends information.A team of scientists from Austria, Canada and Germany have now beamed the quantum state of a particle of light from one island to another 89 miles (143 kilometers) away.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 05 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Quantum Teleportation' Beams Information Farther Than Ever Before
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.space.com/17475-quantum-teleportation-distance-record.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.space.com/17475-quantum-teleportation-distance-record.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				 did a fair amount of sitting on the beach during my vacation this summer. But as any devoted beach goer knows, every hour or so you have to put down your book to adjust your umbrella or your chair's position under it. I got pretty good at predicting the path of the sun throughout the day, so could minimize my effort. Still, the process gave me an appreciation of just how much moving a solar panel has to do to track the sun.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Fri, 07 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Mobile Robots Turn Solar Panels to Follow the Sun
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://spectrum.ieee.org/img/solbot%20copy-1347044560941.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://spectrum.ieee.org/energywise/green-tech/solar/mobile-robots-turn-solar-panels-to-follow-the-sun?utm_source=feedburner&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+IeeeSpectrum+%28IEEE+Spectrum%29
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://spectrum.ieee.org/energywise/green-tech/solar/mobile-robots-turn-solar-panels-to-follow-the-sun?utm_source=feedburner&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+IeeeSpectrum+%28IEEE+Spectrum%29
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				The European Union launched an anti-dumping probe into Chinese solar panels on Thursday after an industry association claimed the products were being exported for less than it costs to make them.The complaint, filed in July by a group of 25 producers of solar gear, including companies from Germany, Italy and Spain, is the biggest-ever anti-dumping claim filed with the EU.China, the world's largest producer of solar panels, accounts for about two-thirds of global production. It exported solar panels and associated key components worth around (euro) 21 billion ($26.5 billion) to the 27-nation bloc in 2011, the EU said in a statement.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Thu, 06 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				EU: Anti-dumping probe into China solar panels
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://upload.eeo.com.cn/2011/0805/1312534973878.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.mercurynews.com/business/ci_21484201/eu-anti-dumping-probe-into-china-solar-panels
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.mercurynews.com/business/ci_21484201/eu-anti-dumping-probe-into-china-solar-panels
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Even in these trouble economic times there are some industries that just maintain their growth, seemingly forever. Semiconductors, those tiny little electronic wonders we find in everything from radios to smartphones and LED lights, are ever increasingly in demand. Just as technologies begin to touch everything in our lives, so does the need for advanced production of these little wonders increase.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Sun, 09 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Infographic: Intel, Samsung and TSMC Surge AheadSemiconductor industry infographic, leaders pull ahead of the pack.
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://www.pamil-visions.net/wp-content/uploads/2012/09/semiconductor.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.theepochtimes.com/n2/technology/infographic-intel-samsung-and-tsmc-surge-ahead-289420.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.theepochtimes.com/n2/technology/infographic-intel-samsung-and-tsmc-surge-ahead-289420.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				State-owned coal producer PT Bukit Asam (PTBA) will team up with Chinese electricity company China Huadian Hongkong Company Ltd. to build and operate a coal-fired power plant in South Sumatra.“The joint venture will be engaged in the production of electricity,” PTBA said in an announcement submitted to the Indonesia Stock Exchange (IDX) on Friday.Under the agreement, PTBA will hold a 45 percent stake in the joint venture, called PT Huadian Bukit Asam Power, while China Huadian will own the other 55 percent.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Sun, 09 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Chinese power firm, PTBA set up joint venture
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.thejakartapost.com/news/2012/09/08/chinese-power-firm-ptba-set-joint-venture.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.thejakartapost.com/news/2012/09/08/chinese-power-firm-ptba-set-joint-venture.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Indonesia is set to have more eyes in its skies with the launch of the Lapan A2 satellite to monitor traffic across its vast maritime expanses.The satellite, weighing 78 kilograms, was designed, assembled and tested in-house by the Institute for Aeronautics and Space (Lapan) and will be the nation’s first satellite running in an equatorial orbit that is equipped with an automated remote-sensing system.Suhermanto, chief of Lapan’s Satellite Technology Center, said the satellite would be launched in mid-2013, piggybacking on India’s PSLV-C23 rocket from its base in Sriharikota, India.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Sat, 01 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Lapan A2 Satellite to Allow Better Monitoring of Archipelago’s Waterways
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://www.thejakartaglobe.com/media/images/medium2/20120901112854873.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.thejakartaglobe.com/tech/lapan-a2-satellite-to-allow-better-monitoring-of-archipelagos-waterways/541648
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.thejakartaglobe.com/tech/lapan-a2-satellite-to-allow-better-monitoring-of-archipelagos-waterways/541648
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Paris based sustainable biotechnology developer, DEINOVE (Alternext Paris: ALDEI) and its partners in the DEINOL program have isolated and optimised a strain of Deinococcus bacteria able to generate biofuel from wheat-based biomass and wastes. 
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Mon, 17 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Bacteria Turns Waste to Fuel in Single Stage Process
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.waste-management-world.com/index/display/article-display/6173892650/articles/waste-management-world/biological-treatment/2012/09/Bacteria_Turns_Waste_to_Fuel_in_Single_Stage_Process.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.waste-management-world.com/index/display/article-display/6173892650/articles/waste-management-world/biological-treatment/2012/09/Bacteria_Turns_Waste_to_Fuel_in_Single_Stage_Process.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				MANILA, PHILIPPINES – A more sustainable and efficient bus rapid transit system funded by the Asian Development Bank (ADB) will help decongest the crowded streets of Ulaanbaatar, one of Asia’s fastest growing cities.“Ulaanbaatar is a boom town bursting with people and vehicles. For the long-term livability of the city, its growth needs to be managed to ensure it’s sustainable, and to allow greater access to the wide array of economic opportunities and social services available to its residents,” said Raushan Mamatkulov, Senior Urban Development Specialist at ADB.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Mon, 17 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				ADB Greenlights Mongolia's Sustainable Urban Transport Program
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://www.tema.ru/jj/ub2006.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.adb.org/news/adb-greenlights-mongolias-sustainable-urban-transport-program
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.adb.org/news/adb-greenlights-mongolias-sustainable-urban-transport-program
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				American companies operate as they shift production back to the United States using the humanoid robot to save on costs. Rethink Robotics unveiled its flagship product to the public Sept. 18.“Roboticists have been successful in designing robots capable of super-human speed and precision. What’s proven more difficult is inventing robots that can act as we do—in other words, that are able to inherently understand and adapt to their environments,” said company founder Rodney Brooks, an artificial intelligence legend and robotics pioneer having spent much of his life teaching at MIT. Rethink was founded in 2008 with the purpose of designing a robot like Baxter and carries a few other products. It is currently owned by venture capital firms and Brooks.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Mon, 17 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Humanoid Robot to Revolutionize U.S. ManufacturingRethink Robotics unveils Baxter, a robot that can work alongside humans
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://www.theepochtimes.com/n2/images/stories/large/2012/09/19/rethink_400-590x393.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.theepochtimes.com/n2/technology/humanoid-robot-to-revolutionize-u-s-manufacturing-293789.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.theepochtimes.com/n2/technology/humanoid-robot-to-revolutionize-u-s-manufacturing-293789.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Joule Unlimited, a startup whose engineered microörganisms produce ethanol from sunlight, water, and carbon dioxide, announced the commissioning of a new demonstration plant last week that will start producing ethanol within the next few weeks. Today, the company announced a partnership with Audi that will help Joule develop and test its fuels. The financial details of the partnership weren't released, but not including the Audi partnership, Joule has raised $110 million.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Mon, 17 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Audi Backs Biofuel Startup
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://www.technologyreview.com/files/91222/joulex616.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.technologyreview.com/news/429245/audi-backs-a-biofuels-startup/
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.technologyreview.com/news/429245/audi-backs-a-biofuels-startup/
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				IMTS 2012 came with a vengeance and left us wanting more (more time to see and discover, more rest for our legs, and more IMTSTV and Twitter feeds to help us keep up)! While I verified what some of the preliminary findings suggested for potential manufacturing trends: converging technologies, mobile data solutions and the continued emergence of additive manufacturing and technology equipment interoperability … there were a few stand-outs better understood in-person.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 19 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Technology Round-Up from IMTS 2012
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.imts.com/show/newsletter/insider/article.cfm?aid=513
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.imts.com/show/newsletter/insider/article.cfm?aid=513
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				IMTS 2012 Registration Reaches 100,200 Marking the Highest Show-to-Show Increase EverChicago, Ill. … Results for the 29th edition of IMTS – The International Manufacturing Technology Show 2012 prove the continuing leadership of manufacturing in the overall economy as Show Management reports the strongest results in more than a decade. Hosting exhibitors and visitors from 119 countries, IMTS 2012, which ran Sept. 10-15 at Chicago’s McCormick Place, covered 1.248 million net square feet of exhibit space with 1,909 exhibiting companies.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 19 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				IMTS - The International Manufacturing Technology Show 2012 Proves Continued Strong Manufacturing Picture
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.imts.com/media/imts_releases/20120919.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.imts.com/media/imts_releases/20120919.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				ABB, the leading power and automation technology group announced that it has introduced several new software applications for the marine market that will help all types of ocean vessels dramatically reduce their fuel consumption. These Advisory Systems include the latest versions of ABB’s energy management system for marine applications (EMMA) and Amarcon’s Octopus solution.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 19 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				ABB Launches Complete Marine Advisory &amp; Automation System to Improve Fuel Efficiency
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.maritime-executive.com/article/abb-launches-complete-marine-advisory-automation-system-to-improve-fuel-efficiency
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.maritime-executive.com/article/abb-launches-complete-marine-advisory-automation-system-to-improve-fuel-efficiency
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Thermoelectric power essentially turns heat into electric power, a source which is as yet highly infeasible. While we generate a lot of heat through vehicles and in factories, even the best thermoelectric equipment can actually convert only a fraction of it.However, researchers have been able to create a new material from lead telluride which, they believe, can significantly improve the effectiveness of thermoelectric power generation.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 19 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Thermoelectric power may become more feasible with new material
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://cdn2.ubergizmo.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/09/thermoelectric-power.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.ubergizmo.com/2012/09/thermoelectric-power-may-become-more-feasible-with-new-material/
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.ubergizmo.com/2012/09/thermoelectric-power-may-become-more-feasible-with-new-material/
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Alachua-based biotechnology company Pasteuria Bioscience is being acquired by Swiss agribusiness giant Syngenta in a deal worth up to $113 million, the companies announced Wednesday.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 19 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Alachua biotech firm Pasteurica Bioscience sold for $113M
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.gainesville.com/article/20120919/ARTICLES/120919438
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.gainesville.com/article/20120919/ARTICLES/120919438
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				VENTURES AFRICA – Africa’s largest cement production company, Dangote Cement has revealed plans to open more cement depots across the Nigeria as part of  its strategy to drive down the cost of cement in the country and make the product more accessible  to the consumers.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 19 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Africa’s Largest Cement Company Poised To Open More Cement Depots On The Homefront
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.ventures-africa.com/2012/09/africas-largest-cement-company-poised-to-open-more-cement-depots-on-the-homefront/
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.ventures-africa.com/2012/09/africas-largest-cement-company-poised-to-open-more-cement-depots-on-the-homefront/
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Tech-Clarity Perspective: Best Practices for Developing Industrial Equipment – Top Performers Drive Growth and Profitability with Advanced Design Practices and Enabling Technology explores best practices used by top performing industrial equipment manufacturers. The report shares insights from a survey of over 350 industrial equipment companies, and indicates what those that have most successfully grown their revenue and margins over the last two years do differently in product design and development.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 29 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				BEST PRACTICES FOR DEVELOPING INDUSTRIAL EQUIPMENT
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://tech-clarity.com/ie-survey-2/2439
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://tech-clarity.com/ie-survey-2/2439
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Bailey International perfectly illustrates the reshoring of manufacturing currently taking place across the United States as it begins to reinvest back into America
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 29 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Demonstrating the benefits of reshored manufacturing
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.manufacturingdigital.com/innovators/demonstrating-the-benefits-of-reshored-manufacturing
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.manufacturingdigital.com/innovators/demonstrating-the-benefits-of-reshored-manufacturing
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				From CAD to CNC machining, the digitalization of manufacturing is helping bring work back to America. (Photo credit: Wikipedia)There is a lot of buzz around the re-shoring of manufacturing. Re-shoring refers to manufacturing that was previous done outside of America and has been moved back to America. You will also hear the term near-shoring which refers to manufacturing work that has returned closer to America in countries such as Mexico as an example.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 27 Jun 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Is the Re-shoring of Manufacturing a Trend or a Trickle?
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/6/6c/Small_CNC_Turning_Center.jpg/800px-Small_CNC_Turning_Center.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://www.forbes.com/sites/mitchfree/2012/06/27/is-the-re-shoring-of-manufacturing-a-trend-or-a-trickle/
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.forbes.com/sites/mitchfree/2012/06/27/is-the-re-shoring-of-manufacturing-a-trend-or-a-trickle/
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Construction of the first phase of Samsung's NAND flash plant in Xi'an, Shaanxi province, involving a total investment of $7 billion, kicked off on Wednesday.The facility is expected to become fully operational by the end of 2013, when it will have a monthly output of 100,000 chips and annual sales of 66 billion yuan ($10.4 billion).
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Thu, 13 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Samsung launches $7b Xi'an high-tech factory
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.chinadaily.com.cn/business/2012-09/13/content_15754909.htm
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.chinadaily.com.cn/business/2012-09/13/content_15754909.htm
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Mahindra inaugurated its new Technical Center in Troy, Michigan today. This facility is the company's first technical center in the USA and will leverage Michigan's large automotive talent pool to provide design and consulting services for Mahindra's automotive customers in the region. This new facility will initially employ 25 engineers and has been designed to accommodate double that number in the future.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 19 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Mahindra Opens Technical Center in North America
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.theautochannel.com/news/2012/09/19/050315-mahindra-opens-technical-center-north-america.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.theautochannel.com/news/2012/09/19/050315-mahindra-opens-technical-center-north-america.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				SAN JOSE -- The strangest thing you'll find inside the headquarters of digital-sign-maker Altierre is not the 25,000-square-foot, fully-stocked supermarket that no one shops in, though that's pretty strange. No, the strangest thing is the dozens of factory workers there who are building and testing the company's electronic signs -- work that until a year ago was done in China.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Tue, 18 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Altierre sees automation as key to Silicon Valley manufacturing
  			</title>
  			<link>
  				http://www.mercurynews.com/breaking-news/ci_21575100/cassidy-altierre-sees-automation-key-silicon-valley-manufacturing
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://www.mercurynews.com/breaking-news/ci_21575100/cassidy-altierre-sees-automation-key-silicon-valley-manufacturing
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  		<item>
  			<description>
  				Brazil's defense industry is booming, fueled by government incentives to modernize the country's armed forces and develop a robust, export-oriented military industrial complex.
  			</description>
  			<pubDate>
  				Wed, 22 Aug 2012 00:00:00 GMT
  			</pubDate>
  			<title>
  				Brazil's defense industry booms
  			</title>
  			<media:thumbnail height="75" url="http://l3.yimg.com/bt/api/res/1.2/2g_LedMhJg8C6lhCVUEBfg--/YXBwaWQ9eW5ld3M7Y2g9MzQxO2NyPTE7Y3c9NTEyO2R4PTA7ZHk9MDtmaT11bGNyb3A7aD0xMjc7cT04NTt3PTE5MA--/http://media.zenfs.com/en_us/News/afp.com/photo_1345657279421-1-0.jpg" width="75"/>
  			<link>
  				http://news.yahoo.com/brazils-defense-industry-booms-174245914.html
  			</link>
  			<guid>
  				http://news.yahoo.com/brazils-defense-industry-booms-174245914.html
  			</guid>
  		</item>
  	</channel>
  </rss>